Theïa Flynn

E-mail: theia.flynn@gmail.com Tel: 078.119.27.32

Web: rangement.github.io

Back from a year in New York where I worked as a teacher and designer, I look forward to redirecting my skills and experiences towards innovative projects.

Skills • Adobe Creative Suite, CSS, ES6/Javascript, Github, Processing, Unity, Robofont, typography, type and web design, vector illustration, risograph printing. Bilingual (French and English), German and Italian at B1 level. Comfortable with any teaching and administrative tasks.

Experience

Remote

05.2020 - Present

New York, NY

09.2019 - 09.2020

Providence, RI 09.2018 – 06.2019

New York, NY 06.04. – 08.20.2018

Providence, RI 06.2017 – 05.2019

Providence, RI 09.2016 – 12.2017

Freelance web design work

• Recently started doing freelance web design work commissioned by independent professionals.

The Language Workshop for Children NYC

• Administrator, in charge of management, enrollments, planning and communication with clients and teachers. Helped the school transition to remote learning starting March 2020.

• French and crafts teacher for children, aged 6mo to 10yrs.

Risograph monitor

• Provided technical assistance and creative advising to students and faculty for printing on the Risograph. Initiated and trained new individuals and groups to using the machine.

Verdes NYC Design Intern

• Worked on branding work for H&M and startups, such as Tuft.

• Budget management, ideation and production for the creation and the running of a one-week Pop-up shop on Canal St.

RISD Fleet Library Photo Archive

• Assisted patrons in research pertaining to the visual archive, rentals and visits. Summer of 2017 and following semesters.

Teaching Assistant in Design Foundation

• For Alejandro Borsani (09.2017 – 12.2017) and for Paula

Gaetano (09.2016 - 05.2017).

 Assisted both faculty members in their respective First Year Design studio classes focused on physical computing and

coding.

Providence, RI

Education

06.2017 - 05.2019

Buenos Aires, Argentina

01. - 02.2017

Berlin, Germany 07. – 08.2016

Rhode Island School of Design

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design 2019, • Honors

Concentration in Technology and Culture.

Espacia Nixso Studio, San Telmo

• "High-Low Tech", Abroad Interdisciplinary Elective.

Technische Universität Berlin

Programming in Java Summer Program.